=Seal of Love= (Season 1)
= ختم الحب = (الموسم الأول)
=Episode 20=
= الحلقة 20 =
♪In regret someone's no longer happy♪
♪ مع الأسف لم يعد أحدهم سعيدًا ♪
Why?
لماذا ا؟
I'm exhausted.
أنا مرهق.
♪Our first meeting♪
لقائنا الأول
♪Was sealed by time♪
كانت مختومة بالزمن ♪
♪Who can I tell♪
♪ من أستطيع أن أقول
Live a good life for me.
عش حياة جيدة بالنسبة لي.
♪I miss you so much♪
♪ اشتقت لك كثيرا ♪
♪When I'm all alone♪
♪ عندما أكون بمفردي
(There's no hope unless you live.)
(ليس هناك أمل إلا إذا كنت تعيش.)
♪Year after year♪
♪ سنة بعد سنة
♪Everything changes♪
♪ كل شيء يتغير
♪Bit by bit in a few nights♪
♪ شيئًا فشيئًا في بضع ليال ♪
♪I watch the stars flicker♪
♪ أشاهد النجوم تومض
♪You're too far away♪
♪ أنت بعيد جدا ♪
Jing Yuan, you did a great job.
جينغ يوان ، لقد قمت بعمل رائع.
♪Why don't I dare to forget you♪
♪ لماذا لا أجرؤ على نسيانك
Haw-haw.
هاو-هاو.
♪I weep as I write♪
أبكي وأنا أكتب ♪
♪Flowers and plants fade♪
♪ الزهور والنباتات تتلاشى ♪
♪In declining years♪
♪ في سنوات الانحدار ♪
Leader said these women are here.
قال الزعيم هؤلاء النساء هنا.
We must take them back today.
يجب أن نعيدهم اليوم.
She's the wicked girl.
إنها الفتاة الشريرة.
It's her who will get us killed.
هي التي ستقتلنا.
Yes, it's her fault.
نعم ، هذا خطأها.
She must have messed with someone.
لابد أنها عبثت مع شخص ما.
Wicked girl.
شرير فتاة.
You'd better mind your own business.
من الأفضل أن تهتم بشؤونك الخاصة.
Don't come over.
لا تأتي.
Stay away.
ابق بعيدا.
Keep back!
ابقى للوراء!
Don't get any closer!
لا تقترب أكثر!
Go, go.
انطلق ، انطلق.
Chief,
رئيس،
you gave the antidote to Yuan that easily.
لقد أعطيت اليوان الترياق بسهولة.
Don't you worry that he'll betray us?
ألا تقلق من أنه سيخوننا؟
Betray us?
تخوننا؟
Soul-eating Sorcery
الشعوذة الآكلة للنفس
has no antidote.
ليس له ترياق.
Then...
ثم...
One needs hope.
يحتاج المرء إلى الأمل.
Then when he's disappointed,
ثم عندما يشعر بخيبة أمل ،
he'll be more desperate.
سيكون أكثر يأسًا.
They haven't got very far. Pursue them!
لم يبتعدوا كثيراً.  قم بإقناعهم!
♪In the next life May everything be in peace♪
في الحياة الآخرة ، عسى أن يكون كل شيء في سلام
♪Back in the hometown Obsessions linger♪
♪ العودة في مسقط رأس الهواجس باقية ♪
♪Pursuing the skinny love I just can't get over it♪
♪ أسعى وراء الحب النحيف الذي لا يمكنني تجاوزه
♪Dying together only exists in the legend♪
الموت معًا موجود فقط في الأسطورة
♪Memories fade away♪
الذكريات تتلاشى ♪
♪Why must I be heartbroken for someone merciless♪
♪ لماذا يجب أن أكون حزينة من أجل شخص لا يرحم
♪A perfect marriage appears in the dream♪
الزواج المثالي يظهر في الحلم ♪
♪But a dream ends anyway♪
♪ لكن الحلم ينتهي على أي حال
♪The wind blows The leaves fall Be away♪
تهب الرياح الأوراق تسقط كن بعيدًا ♪
♪Dying together only exists in the legend♪
الموت معًا موجود فقط في الأسطورة
♪Memories fade away♪
الذكريات تتلاشى ♪
♪Why must I be heartbroken for someone merciless♪
♪ لماذا يجب أن أكون حزينة من أجل شخص لا يرحم
♪A perfect marriage appears in the dream♪
الزواج المثالي يظهر في الحلم ♪
♪But a dream ends anyway♪
♪ لكن الحلم ينتهي على أي حال
♪The wind blows The leaves fall Be away♪
تهب الرياح الأوراق تسقط كن بعيدًا ♪